In the not-too-distant future,
somewhere in time and space,
Mike Nelson and his robot
pals are caught in a nasty place.
They try to survive
the wrath of Pearl
just an evil gal who
wants to rule the world.
From her castle below, she
sets her sights above
just to torture all her captives
on the satellite of love.
Get me down!
I'll send him cheesy movies,
the worst I can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all,
and I'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind, Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity
with the help of his robot friends.
Robot roll call!
Cambot
You're on.
Gypsy
Oh my god!
Tom Servo
Check me out.
Crow.
I'm different!
If you're wondering how he
eats and breathes
and other science facts
just repeat to yourself:
it's just a show...
I should really just relax.
For Mystery Science Theater 3000.
Well, howdy folks. Mike Nelson here,
and welcome to the satellite of love.
Richard Attenborough.
Before we get started,
I should tell you that I
just put my hands in
something very cold and wet. Ick!
Mike, you interrupted our
wet t-shirt contest.
Your...
Wet t-shirt contest.
You know, the favorite
form of entertainment in
Florida, Southern California,
and parts of Wisconsin.
Yeah.
Okay, and these would be your wet t-shirts.
Right-o.
Well, I won with my Wafflenet crew neck,
which absorbed a full 1.35 liters of water.
And while Crow won the day, my Hanes beefy
tee absorbed faster with less dripping.
But we're not quite
sure still what the
whole big deal is over
wet t-shirt contests.
I have to have a little talk with my
robots, and we'll be right back after this.
Okay.
Um, Mike?
What's happening?
I don't know.
Usually, we go only to be right back.
Well, we're not.
Could you do something, please?
Okay.
Hang on.
Again.
We'll be right back.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, hell, I'm leaving.
Mike, jiggle something or something.
Okay.
Uh, you know, maybe...
Excuse me.
Maybe it's this piece of...
Come on.
Ah!
Okay.
There we go.
We'll be right back, I hope.
Really.
Hi, and welcome back to the satellite...
Whoa!
Hey, what's going on?
Why, it's Martin Van Buren,
our nation's eighth president.
Yeah.
Uh, camera, could you
do something about that?
Ah-ha!
There we go.
Okay, thanks.
Anyway, we've got a lot to
do today, so if we could, uh...
Hey, hey, now there's another guy,
and he was trying to say something.
What?
Oh, it was probably Martin Van
Buren again, and he was trying to say,
Hi, I'm Martin Van Buren, eighth
president of the United States.
I was born in Kinderhook, New York.
How would you stop with
the Kinderhook, New York?
Mike, the ship is ten years old.
You've got to expect
these kind of malfunctions.
Yeah, I just got this cup
of coffee from the food
synthesizer, and it gave
me corn niblets instead.
Ew, corn with half and half
and sweet and low? Yuck.
Well, I take my corn
black, so it's not a problem.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Attention! Attention!
The ship is undergoing multiple malfunctions,
and they're increasing geometrically.
Man.
Just thought I'd let
you stupid idiots know.
Yaa, stupid idiots?
Gyps, did we do something to offend you?
Oh, cram it, you meat puppet.
I don't have time for
your constant whiny crap.
Wow.
Oh, wow, man.
Well, you know, she
does have a point, Mike.
That's true.
Oh, can't you see Gypsy's
malfunctioning like everything else?
Wow.
Let me get a hold of Pearl.
Hey, Pearl.
Pearl.
Hello, Pearl.
Our wessel is malfunctioning.
Uh, vessel.
Right.
Vessel.
Oh, hold on a second, Mike.
Just let me check to see if I care.
Uh, oh, um, no.
Seems like I don't.
Um, brain guy, do you care?
Hmm.
Wow.
Um, let me check.
Just see if I care.
Uh, no.
No, it seems like I don't care.
Bobo?
How come I always gotta be the thimble?
...Bobo says no.
Oh, and now the shower's not working.
Oh, Mike, it's only been three minutes.
Oh, man.
Well, he does tend to perspire heavily.
Pearl, can you help at all, huh?
You.
You want to help him out, brain guy?
Hmm.
Wow.
Uh, well, of course I'd like you to know.
Me neither.
Oh, come on, you guys.
We gotta help them out.
Otherwise, they'll die, and we
won't have anybody to play with.
Bobo, you're right.
Oh.
Mike, I find that in
times of crisis, watching
a skin-peelingly bad
movie can truly help.
To that end, I offer you the
balm that is Soultaker, a movie
which an ambitious young
lady wrote for herself to star in.
I now turn over your
healing process to her.
Brain guy, you want to
send him the movie there?
Hmm.
Wow.
Games over powder.
Oh, look, I'd love to do it.
Just a little hard with your eyeball.
I'm interested.
Ow.
There you go.
That's it.
That's fine.
Oh, my God.
Hey, what the?
Oh, look now, these stupid doors.
Try manually, Mike.
Well, I guess we just
can't watch the movie.
God.
Oh, no.
What a mess.
Hey, my seat won't go down.
There.
Please.
Dr. Bates, I'm going to fall down.
Johnny Cash.
Well, good luck having the baby, honey.
I've got tickets to the game.
Because you're mine, I
walk the intensive care unit.
Dr. Blair, Dr. Blair, Dr. Jay
Hamilton, Dr. Jay Hamilton.
I don't like the new
candy striper uniforms.
Fish filleting gloves.
I guess I don't need those.
I'm Ed Bradley.
I'm Steve Croft.
I'm Leslie Stahl.
Time for your meds.
It's the right thing to do.
Oh, you can't even tell he's had a baby.
I've got stigmata, but you don't.
I'll just borrow your
liver for just a minute.
Oh, it's Rocky Mountain, eh?
The death of Helmut Kohl.
The magic fingers have gone berserk.
Whoa, whoa!
You're on a glatchy.
He uses Ghostbusters technology.
This is your brain on death.
Any questions?
Could I have some more applesauce?
You know, it's just not death with dignity
if there's an Estevez in the room.
No.
Hang on.
A couple of strands of soul got
stuck to the tape on my mouth.
Think he's hourly, or does he
get paid on a per-soul basis?
See, if he'd put the club on his
soul, this would not have happened.
Well, I'm going to head down to
T.J. Melonberry's for Coors Light.
George Clooney's taking his shirt off.
Oh, he's dead.
Time for cigarette break.
Soup taper?
What?
Let it get a little closer.
All right.
The soup taker!
Does anything really star Joe Estevez?
Isn't that kind of an oxymoron?
Some kind of moron.
Ooh!
Hey, it's Jim McMahon.
I bet you could never get the
smell of Hardee's out of that car.
No.
Shouldn't he also be talking on
the cell phone and eating yogurt?
If he gets any closer, he's
going to get stuck in her hair.
I'm charmed by the fact that
he almost side-swiped me.
Come here, boy.
Yeah, crank that, Sansui.
Oh, that's a screenwriter and star.
Pearl told me.
I want to look my best if I'm
going to see the motels tonight.
Do I want to look like
David Bowie or Mary Gross?
No, this would be more appropriate
for a Thompson Twins concert.
Well, that's not a dress.
That's a cake.
Hmm, I sure look forward to
that Michael J. Fox movie tonight.
She does all right in
her date entry salary.
Shouldn't her?
That must be Lucille.
Hi, Mr. Whitmiller.
Is Natalie ready?
I don't think Natalie is ever ready.
That's not Natalie.
That's Tonya Harding.
Story by, so there will be a story.
Okay, that's encouraging.
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm, I love you, Scott Baio.
This was before I grew a torso.
When he used to carry me around.
This must be the all-white snake station.
Why do you suppose there's
flex of blood on the wall?
He's going to start a
radio hitting business.
People showing up places.
Your movie, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, a tough morning
choosing between acid washed
or blasted denim.
Music to spin donuts by.
Come on, man.
I still got to pick up Tommy.
Let me wake up the rest of Minuto.
Hang on.
Hi, Mr. Taylor.
I'm Bob Vila.
I won't return your greeting.
Oh, man.
Please don't ever stop being the 80s
when my life is over.
You're dead, Nancy Kerrigan.
I like it when I see me.
Natalie?
Karen's here.
Uh, just a second, Dad.
I'll be right down.
Here, I'll put this in my loser
ex-boyfriend picture drawer.
See you, Bob.
Yeah, sure.
Whoever you are.
Later.
We are planning to rock.
Hey, when are you ever going
to get that thing fixed, anyway?
I still got to take the pistons out.
But hey, I'm finished grinding the valves.
He's preparing for the
mother of all comb-overs.
I never want to make enough
money to pay someone to do that.
You know how.
Hey, Brad.
Well, can't we just rock?
And that's over.
Hey, I'm just kidding, man.
Chill out, will you?
I don't do that stuff anymore.
Really.
He used band roll-on on his lips.
Hey, let's get out of here.
By the way, do you wear your sunglasses at night
so you can, so you can keep track of the visions
in your dreams?
Ooh.
I've met kids today putting their cars in
reverse, backing carefully out of driveways.
Short for summer festering.
Yep.
Well, the balloons have
certainly convinced me it's fun.
I thought we had enough gas.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, that took my soul right there.
Picked up Jimmy Page.
Oh, now they're parking my Brad DeVille.
You better believe it, man.
I'm psyched.
I'm going to score me a funnel cake.
Everybody fast.
Woo.
Hey, what are you looking for?
Nothing.
Looking for Natalie.
Natalie?
Hey, so what if I am?
Hey, this sounds like a real interesting conversation,
you guys, but I'll check you guys out later.
And since no one knows
who I am, it won't really matter.
What?
I can't believe you, man.
How many times do I have to tell
you that Natalie McMillan is a rich man?
Hmm?
The only way you're going to get a girl like
that is with money, and you ain't got it.
So forget it.
Yeah?
You don't even know the girl.
Yeah, lucky for me.
You want to go or not?
No, I think I'll just hang
out here for a while.
Fine.
Yeah, come back and get me when
the Teddy Bear Band takes the stage.
Yum, half a mushroom Swiss burger.
Just wait for me under the floor mat, man.
Wow, until this moment, his long hair in back completely
distracted me from the fact that he's balding in front.
Yeah.
The lead singer for Mr. Mr. is concerned.
He's the driver.
He rocks.
Who else?
Hold my finger.
Oh my God, he's a catcher's mitt with eyes.
I want the soul of that
stuffed bunny on the window.
It's Boy George.
What time?
Eight o'clock.
Ooh, can't.
Going to be a lunch taker then.
Is that all?
No.
There's one more.
Just hit her in the leg with a pipe.
Hmm, pricey, but you get to keep the glass.
Hey, I've seen you.
Where?
Right over there.
Don't point.
Sorry, sorry.
What should I do?
Should I go over and say hi to her?
I would.
Natalie!
Natalie McMillan, I thought you moved away.
Where have you been?
College.
Where?
New York.
New York?
Why so far away?
It makes stalking you hard.
I made kind of a deal with my dad.
Well, it's great to see you.
Come on, let's dance.
I'm Gino Vanelli.
He's John Stamosing.
Mm-hmm.
There.
That was a good song.
Ahoy, darling.
Well, hi.
I'm Sticky Maked.
It's an Amish band.
Hi, I'm indeterminately a man.
I want to be happy today.
Found a gay man.
Just off for the Anything Goes rehearsal.
Want to hear me do Super Bowl Shuffle?
Enjoy the balloon.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
All I know is we're together.
Hi, I got your baby, remember?
I just got to hang around
and be John Stamos.
Sorry.
Yeah.
You're a girl and stuff.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
I was assaulted.
It's fun.
I want to be happy today.
What's your name?
I'm Debbie.
Natalie.
She reminds me of someone
I knew a long time ago.
Reba McIntyre.
Just someone I used to know.
Man, that guy's got a small face.
Now, just the Mennonites.
Thank you.
Our hand-hewn wood CDs
are available to the gate.
Oh, no.
Balloons.
I hate balloons.
Trees.
Convertible cars.
Oh, no.
I'm overwhelmed.
Well, hey, can I call you sometime?
We can go to the George Will concert.
Sorry.
Love is lifting me up where I belong.
Karen!
The lace on my skate broke.
That airs out my armpits.
Hey, Zach.
Man, I'm really proud of you.
I made it through the whole afternoon
without asking Natalie to dance.
Yeah, I wanted to.
Every time I got the
nerve up, she disappeared.
Too bad it's not for good.
You know, I could be saying it has
ballooned so many times right now.
Well, it's noon.
Summerfest is over.
Oh, no.
It's Kathy Griffin.
Hey, where's Zach?
Take a guess.
A polishing or scrimshaw collection?
Oh, that idiot.
Natalie.
Jeff Kalealy did it.
Zach.
Hi.
How you been?
Great.
When did you get back in town?
Last night.
So, what have you been doing?
How would I know?
I've been taking night
classes at the college.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, what are you taking?
Well, it's a business course.
I want to own my own business.
Restoring old cars?
You remembered.
Well, we did go out for five years
and just broke up two weeks ago.
What are you doing?
Who are you waiting for?
Karen.
Well, where is she?
She went somewhere with John.
I don't know.
She's with her John?
She just left you here?
No, I'm sure she's going
to be back eventually.
You know, there's a Summerfest next year.
She'll probably show up for that.
Come on, now.
Let's go.
Where are you Skinner's on?
Just a minute.
Come on.
I hate to leave you here like this.
Well, she's got to come back for a car.
Right.
Tomorrow, maybe.
Not tonight.
Come on.
Come with us.
Are you sure it's okay?
I'm so sure.
Come on.
Just move those one-hitters
out of the way there.
Aye.
Oh, I think I just sat in
someone's Cheezerito.
What's this?
Natalie needs a ride.
But she's upper-middle class,
and we're slightly lower-middle.
Well, let's go to Centerville's Summerfest.
Hey, I really do walk the line.
Hi, folks.
You may be wondering if I'm Martin Sheen.
Well, I'm not.
Turns out I'm his vastly more
talented, yet less appreciated brother.
Thank you.
Did the big chin say 8 or 8.30?
I'm at Bradley.
They are, in fact, traveling down the
road, and they are floating with disaster.
My lunch is about to do a round trip, dude.
Whoa.
Wow, it's the virtual drunk idiot game.
Come on, Brad.
What's the hurry?
I'm in no hurry, man.
I'm simply rocking.
I'm never in a hurry.
Oh, I like it getting carsick.
Well, that's because you're reading.
Put that down.
Sorry.
Flashing back to other people's memories.
Slow down.
I mean, you better slow down.
Sorry, I can't drive 55.
Slow down now!
Make it.
Leak taker.
Where's David Byrne's head?
He's Billy Idol.
Son of a...
You're gonna kill us all!
Hi.
I'm a tree.
Just want to put in a good word or
two for nature, since the camera's on me.
Thanks for your time.
Man, I love that cord.
Save the balloon!
I hope we were thrown
violently out of the movie.
Damn.
She is survived by her dance skins.
Oh, rollin' voice, my Joe.
We got thrown from the
car in an equidistant fashion.
I hope they didn't hurt their
tight pants points hardly renown.
Well, we lost the meaningless
red-headed woman.
Dummy, didn't you see that
warning Joe Estevez crossing sign?
At least my spiral perm wasn't damaged.
Ooh.
Triple Salcow really takes it out of you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm tied.
What the hell happened?
I don't know.
I think we hit a train or something.
Something, I don't know.
Maybe a cucumber.
It's some son of a...
Standing right in the middle of the road.
We crashed?
It's her fault for being rich.
If y'all hadn't been yelling so
much, I probably could have made it.
You know, we must have
gotten thrown clean from the car.
Where is the car?
We learned how to drive, Brad.
Hey, why don't you just shut up?
Yeah?
You know, this is really weird.
None of us even got hurt.
Wait a minute.
Where's my balloon?
What?
Ooh, man.
Candace.
Wait a minute.
Something is definitely wrong.
The whirlpool is ice cold.
Life support is failing,
and there's a mysterious
ship keeping pace with us
and holding us in its trektamine.
Oh, my gosh.
An alien presence is attacking us.
What do we do, Mike?
What do we do?
Uh, turn it over to Gypsy.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Much on this.
Oh, great.
Gypsy's hopeless.
You better take command, Mike.
Ah, me?
Yeah, we're losing time, Mike.
Lead us.
Inspire us.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, I'm in command.
Good.
Established.
Put alien ship on view screen.
Good.
That'll help.
There.
Uh, yeah, I think we need a
little something more, Mike.
Life support is still failing and all.
Right.
Okay.
Uh, increase magnification.
Uh, Mike, we actually
don't have magnification.
All right.
Just a little bit magnification.
And good.
All right.
Uh, shields up.
Shields?
What the hell does he smoke?
Arm photon torpedoes.
Mike, uh, we only had that one photon torpedo,
but, uh, Crow set it off in your locker,
if you'll remember.
That was decent.
Okay, uh, well, then, uh, close hex field.
Whoa.
Whoops.
Uh, there.
I've broken the hex field.
Carry on.
I'll be in my ready room.
Great, Mike.
That's just great.
Uh, we'll be right back.
Uh, you gonna need any corn in there?
Ah.
I'm Marshall Brodine,
a professional magician.
I'm gonna take her soul
and her Garfield keychain.
Her soul has a refreshing mint flavor.
Ew, it smells like Marlboro
Lights and Jovan Musk.
Hot, hot, ooh, hot
soul, hot, ooh, hot, ooh.
Hey, buddy, could you
just hand me your soul?
Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
This man's recently been rocking.
Hey, my hand is covered with bronzer.
Okay, just shove the
irony down our throats.
Oh, jeez.
Man, I'm not gonna reach my quota.
This is what happens when death
is run by low-level bureaucrats.
Michael learned it.
Can you work for me on Thursday?
Thriller!
Where are the other four?
Uh, they're on layaway.
What happened?
Displacement.
You must track them, and you must
abide by the rules of time and space.
Yeah, what are those again?
Quickly.
Don't look at me like that.
Kathy Rigby, paramedic.
Dispatcher says paramedic unit.
Just as I suspected.
Hungry Jack complete.
Just add water.
Hey, it's Hamilton Jordan.
Uncut lick of maid.
I should have known.
Got some griffin done.
Amazing that they weren't all killed.
You find the ID?
We're getting them.
Oh, yeah.
Tell me something.
You see anything about
this picture that doesn't fit?
What do you mean?
I mean that.
The door?
It was open when we got here.
Yeah.
So what do you figure the chances are of a door
opening by itself on impact and a head-on collision?
Quite good, really.
Don't take this the wrong way, Sarge.
Get bent.
I think you're reading too much into it.
It's always the same
argument with us, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go get some stroganoff.
You like firemen?
I sure don't.
Man, my monthly soul
count is really tanking.
I'm never going to win
that set of steak knives.
Oh, sorry.
Is the camera still on?
Jeez.
Okay, I'll get back to it.
They might have left their
souls in the glove compartment.
Frank Boothcam.
Hey, hey, you forgot us!
Stop that!
You forgot four of the passengers, don't!
Shut up.
What's his problem?
People love to hear me talk.
Jeez.
Oh, man.
Please let my Billy
Squire tape still be here.
Oh, man.
Look at it, man.
It's mangled.
We are lucky to be alive.
Whoa, a lot of curly fries under there.
Oh, Candace must have
really been messed up, man.
Do you have any gray coupon?
My majorette boots!
Hey, what are you doing in my car, man?
Hey, wait a minute.
You were the dude that
was in the middle of the road.
You made me wreck my car.
That tightens my pants.
What are you still hanging around here for?
Hmm?
You guys, I think we'd better go.
My nephew made mighty ducks.
Get off!
Ah, he's just panicking to get souls,
because he drew against his commission.
America's most beloved
drug retailer was killed today.
Oh.
Man, he's dead, man.
He's dead!
Hooray, let's tell the town.
Hmm.
Now, how can I possibly get the others?
Perhaps by pursuing them, I
might catch them in some manner.
Hmm.
No messy soul residue.
I think we lost one.
But I'm not going to check.
Hey, Marlboro brand gas.
Three, two, beer run.
Oh, come on, sweetheart.
You know I'd never cheat on you.
Well, I'd never even look at another woman.
Well, this is a man I'm looking at.
Hey, they have turkey jerky here.
Huh?
Well, sure I love you.
Edward Hoppers, Quickie Mart.
Jolene?
What's she got to do with this?
Hey, call the police.
I don't see him.
He's out there somewhere.
We told him to murder somebody.
He's not just going to let us go.
Hey, we need to use your phone.
This guy just killed our friend out there.
He's after us.
Hello?
You expect me to believe that?
I'm telling you the truth.
Come on, get out of here with this crap.
I'm not hanging up till I
get this little matter settled.
What's the matter?
This guy, he won't get off the phone.
He's just ignoring me.
You know I'm getting sick
and tired of your accusations.
Why, it's Harvey.
Hi, Harvey.
Who is that guy?
Have you ever seen him before?
No.
911.
Hello?
I want to make a report
about a murder that happened.
911.
Please state that it's for the emergency.
I want to make a report about
a murder that happened tonight.
Look harder.
You're operating for tomorrow.
She hung up on me.
What is everybody dapping around here?
Looks like he's wearing a seaweed hat.
No, we're not going here.
I'll stay right here where it's safe.
Hey, I think I saw something.
Where?
In East Dubuque.
What do you think?
Right here?
Over there.
It's a tall thing made of
wood with green stuff on top.
Hey, it's probably just a wind tunnel.
Yeah, sorry I kept a
lookout for the psycho killer.
I don't think so.
Hey, what's that?
It's a moose.
What do you think it is?
It's a tow truck.
It's the car!
I love Rick Okasik.
Stop!
Wait!
Sorry, don't have a tow bar.
Happy St. Blaise Day.
Oh, you wearing that?
They went to the old-time
picture booth at Six Flags.
Tonya Harding is Scarlett O'Hara.
Am I a machine or an Estevez?
Mother...
Wait!
No!
Give me your stupid soul!
Remember, you need only
walk briskly to get away from him.
I need condoms.
What now?
Oh, my God!
We forgot Tommy!
We've got to go back and get him!
Look, he's at the store.
He's going to be safe there.
Just get to your house
and call the cops, okay?
Come on.
You're talking, son of a...
He'll kill you, too!
Why don't you listen to me?
I'm watching cops.
If I die, I'm going to die eating
string cheese and fruitopia.
Hey, I just fed the cockroaches.
Here, get me some
whoppers while you're in there.
Why didn't you take the girl
when you had the chance?
You know all the rules.
We still have time.
Not much.
Where does that guy even keep his acorns?
You must restore the
balance or pay the penalty.
Oops.
Police, open up.
My response to spills is to go home.
Keep out.
Oh, foiled again.
Can I put up a lost cat poster?
What do you want?
Do you have a phone so I can
call Martin to take over my role?
Is there money you want, man?
Is that what you want?
Or do you want the new
living room set from Boy Hill?
Got plenty of it, man.
Go ahead, take it.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, man.
Where are the Stewart sandwiches?
Closing time.
Does that mean that every new beginning
comes from some other beginning's end?
I think so.
Yeah, good.
I was playing horsey.
Got a leaky cash register.
I'll race you to film obscurity.
Yep.
Slow and steady wins the soul.
Get a nice antebellum home.
I'm antebellum-y brothers.
Does that count?
Natalie, are you all right?
We've been worried sick about you.
What's going on here?
What is the matter?
Where's Dad?
Are the back doors locked?
He's looking for you.
There's someone out there there.
There's someone out
there who's trying to kill us.
What?
Okay, the doors are locked.
Do you have a gun?
Well, my husband's-
Where is it?
Dad, no.
Where is the gun, Ms. McMillan?
Dad!
Let's call the police and
let them take care of us.
All right.
No, no one is calling anyone
until I find out what this is all about.
Now, what makes you think
someone is trying to kill you?
There's a man out there.
We don't even know who he is.
He killed Brad.
We saw him do it.
Brad did do it.
He's after us.
He chased us here.
Oh, I understand, dear.
I'll get the pampering.
I don't know where, but
he's out there somewhere.
Natalie, come on upstairs and let me
draw you a hot bath with Epsom salts.
Or draw you a tree.
Now?
Mom, I'm not five years old.
I know, sweetheart, but you
need to relax and calm your nerves.
Come on, I'll give you some heroin.
Okay.
Just let me sit here a little bit longer.
I'll follow you up.
Okay, I'll go turn on the water.
I'll do a striptease for it.
I have just got to write
Mom out of this story.
No, she's going to add Mr. Bubble
and give herself a urinary infection.
Being low class, we only
had corncops for windows.
See anything?
No.
Well, I mean, I saw some
of the outside and stuff.
I'm really sorry about
what happened to Brad.
So am I.
And I was going to go to Chess
King tonight, so this just bites.
Well, my dad can take you
home when he gets here.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
I'll just go with the police.
I'll beat myself up and have
myself held without charges.
Well, if I don't see you again, Zach...
It'll be too soon.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah.
Zach, goodbyes are more
effective when someone leaves.
Wait, Natalie.
I really didn't know anything
about the coke in the car tonight.
About Brad.
About anything.
Zach, it's okay.
It's okay.
You're lower class and
stupid, I understand.
Natalie.
Uh, just a second, Mom.
He's making violent love to me, Mother.
It sounds like I'm wanted.
You are?
Rick Springfield after
Monty Clip's accident.
Natalie.
You want Batman crazy foam?
I'm coming, Mom.
Look, can I just help
you take your clothes off?
Mike?
Dumb, Zach.
There, we've fixed every
problem, found every flaw.
What could possibly go wrong, huh?
How about everything?
Go!
Got a light, I love the pearl.
I can't play now.
A soul taker has appeared in the castle
and it's attacking Bobo.
Unhand him, you race.
Get away, pearl one.
I'll save you, Bobo.
I don't know who you are,
but get your soul,
pinching paws off my monkey.
Ah, Pearl Forster.
At last three.
Hey, Pearl, how's it going?
Frank, jeannie's Frank, is it really new?
Come here, Pearl.
Frank, I thought you were dead.
I am dead.
I was in Second Banana Heaven for a while,
but it is so political up there.
Pat Buttram had it in
for me, right for the star.
So then I was an angel for a while,
and then I got into big trouble
for appearing to people as Della Reese.
Scared the hell out of them.
So they transferred me to soul taker.
Oh.
Oh, uh, Frank, brain guy, brain guy, Frank.
When met, deceased one.
Hey, great.
Where'd you get the hostess snowball?
Tell me about it.
So how are Mike and
the bots doing up there?
Oh, well, let's take a look.
Ah, no, we're plummeting
in the Earth's atmosphere.
Gonna be sick.
Whoa!
Give our Mike.
Ah, to thee.
I can't believe it.
This gordita is delicious.
Oh, try a border fry.
Oh, knock, it was horrible.
An unpleasant man tried to steal my soul,
and, oh, hello,
and he had this hair that hit,
uh, him.
Oh, it's him.
Oh, Frank, we have so
much catching up to do.
Let's have some General
Foods International coffee.
Oh, perfect.
And you up there, get
back into the theater.
Hey.
Huh?
Hey, what'd I do?
You didn't do, Jack.
We were saved by a tractor
beam from that mysterious ship.
Cambot, give me rocket number nine.
Why?
Why then, we're saved.
Thanks, gyps.
Yeah, jump up my tube, white boy.
Oh, we got movie fight.
What else?
I wonder if the Natalie's
Bath channel is on.
Did you see a ghost or something?
I could have sworn I heard
something from the exact spot.
Now, how would you know if
it came from this exact spot?
Well, I mean, from somewhere around here.
What were you doing?
I was just putting
something away in the attic.
Your father.
Oh, for a minute there, I thought...
Hmm?
Oh, never mind.
I'm going to lay down for a little bit.
Can you turn off the
water when the tub's full?
Of course.
Thank you so much
for turning off the water.
I'm so glad you were home.
Now they're just gratuitously
postponing the nudity.
She looks like a drag
queen without his wig.
Alfie, what's the matter?
I pooped in my water supply.
Okay.
Interior, bedroom, me.
Draped across the bed, tousled but tawny.
I lay there, hand on my taut tummy.
Still pretty in a worried kind of way.
Zoom in closer to my prettiness.
Closer.
You're going to cut back to me.
Then me.
And more me.
We've got a screenwriter.
She needs a coffee drip.
Stat.
I'm going to bed.
You know, I usually like snuff
films, but this one ain't cutting it.
I don't get it.
What happened to the skeleton?
Huh.
I hear clothes coming off.
It is the same tree, isn't it?
I'm positive it is.
The coast is clear.
I'm ordering a steel cage match on paper.
I don't know, but I think
we better get out of here.
Hey.
This house has all the rooms.
We decided we won the lead.
Is that my tummy, or is
that a raging hell beast?
Hey, they have three-pronged
outlets, those bourgeoisie jerks.
Wipe out.
It's the pantry of death.
Don't miss the terrifying
water-turning offing.
Is there a turkey farm in the hall?
Hump me.
Charlie.
Yeah, beat it, biped.
Don't you remember me?
What's wrong, boy?
Well, I'm really just feeling this
emotional malaise these days.
I don't know.
Good-sized yard.
Plenty of room to rock.
That's okay.
Testicles are overrated.
There's nobody out there?
Oh, that's right.
Dogs can't see idiots.
Okay, you big sissy.
Oh, roof, roof.
Okay.
Man.
You know, this whole bath thing is
getting to be more trouble than it's worth.
Yeah.
I'm ready for our Japanese tea ceremony.
Wow.
Mom looks like Senor Wences' hand.
Mm.
I checked on the tub.
It's got several more hours to go.
Do you plan on looking
like this much longer?
No.
She takes off the wig,
and it's Kevin Bacon.
A huge, mannish turtle.
Oh, no, it's you, Mom.
I must have fallen asleep.
Your bath is ready.
Oh, thanks.
I filled it with golden popcorn topping.
Natalie.
I'm Ann Landers.
I overheard your conversation downstairs.
You're not considering
dating Zach again, are you?
Well, I still have feelings for him.
How could you have feelings for
someone who put your life in danger?
Mom, I thought you liked Zach.
I don't know what you see in him.
Sweaty proletarian pecs.
What did he possibly give you?
You sound just like Dad.
Natalie, listen to me.
Mom, you're hurting me.
I'm not you on your ass, Mom.
So help me.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I was just concerned about you.
I didn't mean to upset you.
It's okay.
I'm going to go withhold
sex from your father.
Finally, possible nudity.
Okay, sit back.
Yes.
Enjoy nudity.
That nude arm.
Woo-hoo.
Oh, my.
Oh, dear.
Now I'm just embarrassed.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Remember when you caught
me doing this to you, Mike?
Yeah.
You need any more water
in the bathtub, honey?
At the top of the news
tonight, a serious car accident
leaves two young people
critically injured and three dead.
We break now for a report.
An official statement, Mayor?
Please, I'd rather not
comment at this time.
Is it true that doctors have informed you
to disconnect all life support
systems for your daughter?
I think it's a personal matter.
Gee, I instantly need counseling.
Just an official comment, Mayor.
You want an official comment?
I proclaim it lick me day.
The doctors have declared my daughter...
Patient of the month.
brain dead.
We have accepted their recommendation
to disconnect all life support systems...
everywhere.
Okay, here it comes.
Oh, I got something in my eye.
What?
Ow.
Come on, hurry up, bro.
It's an underwear suit.
What?
Well, help me out here.
You gotta try it.
Come on, Mike.
Wow.
All right, I'm trying.
Get it out.
Wow.
Damn it.
Keep showing underwear movie.
I'll be right back.
I gotta get this out.
Wow.
Poor guy.
Man, is there even a name
for mom's little sickness here?
A little apharism.
I'll rinse out my fancy hose for you.
Hey, anybody see the visine?
I can't see a thing in here.
Seems she's been using her petaline.
Is there a slower mow available?
Any kind of eye wash?
Anything?
Gypsy, you gotta have eye wash.
That big-ass eye of yours.
Hell no.
You know, if she turns around...
I know, I know.
If that happens, promise me
you won't tell Crow.
Oh, yeah, right.
Sure.
What's going on now, you guys?
It's fine.
You got time.
I'm good.
She's turning around.
Did you say she's turning around?
No, no, Crow.
I said she's spurning a clown.
Well, I like that, too.
I'm a wisdom, visine.
Oh, boy.
How are you going to pull the brush?
Midnight.
Why don't you leave my husband alone?
He's made a statement.
Please give us that privacy.
Mom.
Okay, wait.
I got a Big Sam's Club thing,
a visine in the attic.
I'll be right back.
Ah.
As you can see, Mayor McMillan
is under a great deal
of stress this evening.
St. Joseph's Chief of Staff,
Dr. Richard Reiner,
has informed the News 10
that with parents' permission,
the life support systems
for both Natalie McMillan
and the other surviving passenger,
Zach Taylor,
will be disconnected
at midnight.
All this, plus Andy Rooney...
What?
Please stay.
Sorry, Natalie.
You'll never die.
Four.
A lot of dust bunnies under here.
Daddy, get out of here!
Get out of here!
Now she has to put on
her underwear in slow-mo.
Get your dad's gun!
I'm instantly dressed.
Okay.
I'm all visined up.
I'm coming.
There she is.
Ah, hell, a robe?
What the hell is this?
I saw a lot.
I saw everything.
Shut up, Servo.
Shut up.
Stupid Servo.
The insole taker.
I have an offer for you, Natalie.
Twelve issues for $12.
I've got an offer for you, too.
Let him go!
I'll let him go.
If you come with me.
No!
Let go with him.
Go ahead.
Put him down.
Put him down, I swear I'll shoot!
Take a picture with him
and let him go.
Damn, the battery's dead.
Why don't you try
pulling the other trigger?
That's the kind of personal service
you don't get from other soul takers.
There.
The still pictures are moving faster
than the actual movie.
So a seven iron knocks him cold,
but a gun does nothing.
Mm-mm.
You can't kill a man
that's already dead.
Why don't you leave us alone?
Because you belong with me.
I belong with him!
I'll be scared, Natalie.
I got him.
Mm-mm.
Oof.
Dad!
I've done that on spring break
dozens of times.
I was going to give him
a piggyback ride,
but I slept.
Zach, are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
I thought you were dead.
Are you okay?
Your mom is weird.
I'm fine.
Come on.
So after all that,
no baths.
Mm-mm.
None.
Is that your decision, then?
That's your decision, Shane?
To die with him.
Um, they're gone.
Greg Nouganis
in the role of a lifetime.
Dr. Fletcher?
Please report to
attentive care.
So how dead's your kid?
Zach was really looking forward
to seeing Natalie again.
Well, he saw her, didn't he?
Oh, Grant.
You don't think much
of my boy, do you?
I try not to think
about him at all.
Oh, Grant, please.
I'm sorry.
We're all upset
over what's happened.
Please excuse my husband.
He has a tendency
to say things
he doesn't really mean.
I like fudge.
You don't mean that.
Call for Dr. Wachter.
I hate buses.
Do the buses run this late?
Yes, sister, I checked.
There'll be one
in just a few minutes.
Stop running
or I'll hit you
in the head with a ruler.
The police station
is in that bar.
Hey, the police
can't help us now.
Come on.
We need to get on this bus.
It's supposed
to take us to the hospital.
Oh, my God.
We've got to go back
to my house.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Stop.
What are you doing?
My mom.
He said something
to my mom.
No, no, no.
Your mom is fine.
She's at the hospital.
What?
Hey, look,
you wrote this crap.
When I was at your house,
I saw her on the news.
She's at the hospital.
She's fine.
But she was there.
She hugged me.
That wasn't your mother.
That was that man.
How is that possible?
I don't know,
but look.
They don't see us.
You see that?
Isn't she you?
That clerk didn't see us.
You know,
I'd rather follow the story
of the nuns getting home.
I don't understand any of this.
What's happened to us?
Why don't they see us?
What I know is that
our bodies are at the hospital
and we're here.
Listen,
give me a break.
So we're dead?
Is that what you're saying?
No,
our bodies are being kept alive
with machines at the hospital.
My body's hooked up
to a snowblower.
So how do we get back
to our bodies?
I don't know.
Let's get on this bus
and it'll take us to the hospital.
We can find out
when we get there.
Gee,
your soul smells terrific.
Oh,
I broke this bus driver's
jaw with a Bible once.
Thank you.
It's everyone
with a dead daughter
gets a cup of soup night
here at the hospital.
Grant.
Dr. Elliot,
you can call on two.
Yes,
thank you.
Apparently,
it's on me.
Dr. Reiner
left this for you.
Oh, wow.
I ain't got to go
with the Packers
over the Lions.
Favre's really
kicking butt lately.
Redskins are the charges
for sure.
I don't know
what I'm going to do
without Zach.
Maybe I'll shave my beard.
Ever since his mother died.
Look,
I'm sorry I killed her.
Must you bring it up
every time I see you?
I'm sorry.
You don't want to hear
about my problem.
It's okay,
Mr. Taylor.
We understand.
I'm not saying we care,
but we understand.
The nuns just flip off
the driver
and run off the bus.
Hold on,
my soul isn't wearing
a sports bra.
You know,
most directors forget
to give you
the bus details.
Bus taker.
I'm no good
with sick people.
What am I even
going to say
to my body?
What?
This looks like a bus.
It's all coming together.
Let's go to the cafeteria
first,
see if they've got
any tapioca left.
How do we know
what floor
our bodies are on?
We're just going
to have to check each one.
Souls can press
elevator buttons,
but they can't be shot.
What?
They said on the news
that at 12 o'clock
they're going to cut
the machines off.
By 12th midnight.
Oh, man.
There's tax reasons.
Urkel.
Hey, Urkel.
Weird thing is
he's listening
to Gregorian chants.
You didn't know
I could get jiggy
with it, did you?
Well, I guess
Estevez can become
a member of DeBarge
at any moment.
Man, he's a rich
little of shapeshifters.
You've got to give him that.
I'm Ed Bradley.
Now shut up.
Where are you taking me?
Administration and billing.
7th floor.
Oh, it's one of those
high-class elevators.
Um, aren't you due
on the set of Werewolf?
There is no 7th floor.
Here is where I come from.
So he comes from
a taller building, then.
Apparently.
Can we tempt you
with desserts?
Packers!
Looks like he had to have
a flashback
to remember his best friend.
Oh, I love you, Buttons.
Love.
You don't need
to be frightened, Adley.
Don't you see?
What's happened to you
is extraordinary.
It's very rare
for a soul
to be jarred
from its human host.
Soul will get jarred
off the wild mouse
sometimes.
Huh.
I wonder where
that bus is, Mike.
They're letting us down
on the whole bus thing.
Yeah.
Man, I hate this.
It's so awkward
in elevators.
We're here.
Where's here?
The second level.
My world.
Where I'm more successful
than Martin.
All you have to do,
Natalie, is
say the word
and the door
to my world
will open to you.
What do you mean,
your world?
Who are you?
An angel.
An angel?
I'm almost sure.
I take care of souls.
I can keep you safe.
Like the others
in the wreck?
Let's not fling mud
like that.
I want to go back.
Don't say that back.
I want to go back!
In your world,
only death awaits you.
Take me away from here!
There you are.
You dick, baby.
I don't even care, baby.
Then I'll show you.
Natalie!
Can you hear me?
No, she thinks
you're saying
blah-blah-blah.
You still looking
for her, man?
And your Marconi.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Natalie McMillan
is out of your league, man.
This door is ragging on me
like my idiot friend used to.
It's the blonde guy.
He's become a soul taker.
Show us.
Hurry up and do it!
Come on.
Father dude.
You're still around.
I thought for sure
you'd be dead by now.
Come in.
Okay, if you could just
bring your urine sample
to the desk.
What happened to you, man?
I got a new job.
I didn't even know
I was applying for it.
I make pickups
and deliveries.
So the afterlife
is just vague,
menacing dopes
from our own lives.
That's the ultimate answer.
Uh, don't worry.
You're not on my list.
Art Carfunkel.
Funny gag condom.
You still haven't figured it out,
have you, man?
We have.
Can we go?
Zach,
Led Zeppelin was wrong, man.
Shut up.
There is no stairway to heaven.
Zeppelin's never wrong, man.
There was.
You couldn't buy your way in.
Is Sabbath wrong too, man?
Truth is,
I don't even know
if there is a heaven.
That's all part of it.
They keep us in the dark.
Like a bridge over it.
Eh, got to punch in.
Excuse me.
I don't even really know
what to do here, man.
Yeah, I had this big
masterclass from God,
but I was hammered
the whole time.
Let's see,
you kind of
take the sumbitch here,
look off kind of mystical,
keep the arms straight,
there we go.
Ah, shoot,
I got her last bowl
of jello too.
What did you do to her?
I toasted her ass.
Nothing, man.
She's right here.
Gotta keep it warm
in my pit.
So, how's the babage
in heaven?
Bye-bye.
Brad!
Hey, it's new clear blood.
Hmm.
What the?
Oh, it's a habitrail.
I want to thank you.
Oh, my God.
Imelda Marcos is close by.
Uh, honey, you know, it's 5-2.
Why don't we just do it now?
Call it an early night.
Hey, wow, she's really
improved, but it is midnight.
Sorry.
So you'll feel like I will.
Well, the paper's ready.
Cause I'm ready to kill.
Mom!
Don't let them!
By the way, I ran another EEG.
Stop!
Well, we can run EEGs all
night if it's on your insurance.
No.
She's snuffleupagus.
Sue, I'm not gonna make my tea time, huh?
Thoughts for a moment.
It's all right.
Yeah.
Don't let them do it!
Good luck with this one, pal.
Sheesh!
No, Mom, I wanna live!
You can't go back, Natalie.
Goodbye, Peepy.
Peepy?
She can't hear you or see you.
And if you touched her,
you would only frighten her.
Here's an old door hinge.
It's better this way.
In the human dimension, people die.
They leave you.
With me, you get to be a ring.
Stay with me.
I'll never leave you.
I mean, I'll go to the
store to get groceries.
What about Zack?
Zack is dead.
That's what I said.
Come to my world now,
Natalie, while there's still time.
Come with me.
At this special low fare.
Oh.
Hello?
Kinda need an answer.
Huh.
We're drifting, our orbits decaying, and the
mysterious craft still hovers nearby, dark and ominous.
It did save our lives once, but why?
They're toying with us.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Toying.
Yes.
What?
Who are you?
Look.
Behold.
Oh, it's just Joel.
Yeah, you're gonna get that.
Hey, guys.
Joel!
It's Joel!
Hooray!
Joel's back.
Oh, it's good to see you, man.
Oh, thanks.
Crow, your voice kinda sounds different.
Wow, weird.
Oh, I get it.
You changed your bowling pin.
Smart.
And, Tom, it's good to see
your hoverskirt still operational.
Yep.
It's just great to see you guys, all bright
and shiny and in proper working order.
See, you too, Joel.
Say, how'd you get up here?
Well, I don't want to go into too many details
other than it cost me a ton to get up here.
I'll bet.
When I was down on Earth, I found that
Dr. Forster had sabotaged the satellite of love,
so a lot of the major working components
would self-destruct in ten years.
I knew there was something
weird about that guy.
Yeah.
So I came up here to fix it for you.
Well, Joel, hadn't you better
get started then, maybe?
Oh, I mean, we've got some time.
I mean, what have you guys been up to?
Ah, you know, same old, same old, and you?
Right.
Well, you know, after I crash-landed on the
Outback, I kicked around Australia for a little
while, and then I hooked up with the band
Manor Astroman doing pyrotechnics, finally
made my way back to the Midwest where
I now manage the hot fish shop in Osseo.
Cool.
Hey, guys.
All right, I'm set to...
Oh, hey, who do we got here?
Mike, it's Joel.
He's the guy who made us.
He's gonna fix our ship.
Yeah, I know you.
I'm wearing your tube socks.
Hey, did I hear you say you're
managing a hot fish shop?
Yeah, it's pretty neat.
That's great.
I mean, how do you even get that?
Well, I just had a really good interview.
You know, I'm looking
for an overnight cook.
Are you serious?
Oh, man.
Who am I kidding?
I'm stuck up here.
I'm never gonna get down.
Forget it, man.
Oh, man.
Come on.
Take it easy.
You know, things are
gonna get better for you.
I mean, things change.
All right, yeah.
Well, hey, thanks.
Thanks.
Hey, you kids.
Keep it down.
Hey, hiya, Gypsy.
Bite me.
Oh, I better get going on Gypsy.
I'll talk to you guys later, okay?
Okay, Joel.
See you later.
Bye, Joel.
Bye-bye.
Joel's back.
Yeah.
Think about it.
You know, I mean, I'm stuck up here, and
that guy gets to manage a hot fish shop.
Hey, hey, don't compare yourself, Mike.
It ain't healthy.
Yeah.
We'll be right back.
Bring out the dressing and everything.
Don't go there, man.
Make the three bean salad.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Good to see Joel.
Hope he fixes the ship.
How?
How did this happen to you?
The accident.
Oh, that bites.
You wanna get baked?
I tried to tell him over and over that I didn't
mean to hurt anyone, but they didn't believe
me.
Uh, who would that be now?
I guess it doesn't matter how it happened or
whose fault it was, but if you kill someone,
this is how you have to pay it back.
It really blows.
I need your help.
Man, you owe me.
What do you mean I owe you?
The accident.
Dude.
I wanna live.
I wanna get back into my body.
You're crazy, man.
You can't do that.
How do you know?
You just told me they keep you in the dark.
Well, they gave us some stuff.
I didn't really read it.
And then I spilled the
horsey sauce all over it.
Dude.
Man, they really gonna fry mud tú.
Natalie. Natalie also. Natalie?
Chick harsh is my buzz, dude.
Are you sure she's worth it, Zach?
Does she really love you?
I love her. That's what matters.
That's why I've been stalking her so much.
I don't think they're gonna
fry her for doing a good deed.
Higgs?
They'll probably give you a promotion.
Be able to work the counter, man.
The oncoming elevator has its brights on.
Take my hand.
Who's your date, Ron?
Where are we?
We're on the bug zapper floor.
This is a bridge between the human
dimension and the world of angels.
Connected to a hospital?
You're an angel of death.
Well, associate angel of death.
It's my fate, Natalie.
Just as it is yours.
To cause people to die?
Souls, Joe. Let's get busy.
We don't cause people to die, Natalie.
We merely take their souls
when it's time for them to go.
Yeah, death causing is a
whole other department.
I was chosen to take your soul.
Yeah, sure, I shuffled some papers.
If I don't, no one will.
Is that bad?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Oh, and for technical reasons,
your soul must be naked.
Come with me, Natalie.
All it takes is a kiss.
Sure, but can your soul take Claret?
And we can live together forever.
Oh, no.
Joe's improv-ing this.
A pact between the soul
must be seen with a kiss.
Can't he just bend at the waist
and hug you from arm's length?
Bailey!
Don't tongue the reaper!
Zach, you're alive!
Bailey, run!
You lied to me.
Don't leave me, Natalie.
Come on!
You're boned, man.
Come on, it's thoroughly
past midnight by now.
Elevators, too.
The director does buses and elevators well.
I think this is the
floor you're looking for.
Take a slap.
No problem.
Thanks.
Hey, remember what I told you?
Rock on.
Put it right on the iron.
Right.
Sorry what I said about Zapp.
Oh, better bring a couple of these.
You might need them.
Can't be careful naming after me, man.
Do you really think this is going to work?
Are we going to be able
to get back into our bodies?
Hey, hurry up.
Hey, man, I got to go.
St. Peter's going to be tar.
Extending scene, scene, scene, scene, over long film,
film, film, film, film, f-f-f-f-film, over long film.
Extending scene, over long film.
Oh, my God.
Prudential signs.
Just do it, you dummy.
I'd rather make out than live.
Man, I really need to freshen my make out.
Oh.
Hmm?
Duh.
Natalie?
Oh, I'll rinse and spit.
God help me!
There's no God.
There's just dude.
Come on, Natalie.
Ah, her soul got snagged on her brouche.
Mm-hmm.
I know what they're going through, though.
You know, once I left my soul
on the top of the car and drove off.
That's why I put strips of Velcro along
the edges of my soul to hold it in place.
Sure.
I wish my shop teacher were here.
He'd know what to do.
What is he doing?
Her soul's going to be all
threadbare and worn out.
And stay out, damn kids
nosing around my souls.
Learning to palm the
soul is the tough part.
Something's screwed up,
but I can't call my boss again.
I'll get in trouble.
A guy running through a hospital.
That's new.
Yeah.
Do you feel a lower class breeze?
Wheeling Captain Pike down the hall.
Those balloons cheer me up.
Estevez is on his way to give his
healing through humor workshop.
Ah, don't go in there.
You might find something interesting.
Wow, this is terrific action here.
Now, these ants, they're all over
the jujubee you dropped, Mike.
Look at that.
Man.
They're really fighting.
Look at them go.
It does provide a stark
contrast to the film.
There you go.
It's the THX 1138 stairs.
Ah.
You know, this has action and
nostalgia, because we've seen it before.
Well, Mole, don't do that movie.
Well, there is a seventh floor.
It's Heaven's boiler room.
Yes.
Behind the fluffy surface of Heaven
hums a complex infrastructure.
Drum machine is stuck on.
You know, David Byrne is right, Heaven
is a place where nothing ever happens.
Come on.
You know, you really can see
Akira Kurosawa's influence here.
You know, what with the way there's a
movie going on and stuff, and it's on film.
It's something Hitchcock would have been
proud of, his pet chimpanzee directing.
Boom.
Hey, Zeppelin was right.
There is a stairway to Heaven.
Sure, soul-taking's hard, but it's better
than making cold calls like he used to do.
Alarm!
Schnell!
Mark Schnell!
I ain't gonna kiss you, Estevez.
You can put my green crap
in that ring, but no kissing.
Oh, he's on top of the Heaven building.
You're it.
It's all over now.
Oh, I wish that were true.
I left the house this
morning with three soul rings.
Oh, it's 32K cash memory
brought up a little video.
It's wetting the air out of a
balloon on the way down.
God needs to know when
you're taking your vacation.
It is over now.
Eight plugs pulled, two to go.
Not bad.
Is he dead?
No.
I don't even disconnect the machines.
I was just checking on him.
His father left without sign on the floor.
So, your soul is subject to gravity?
I have so many questions.
Can souls get toe fungus?
Can I still have butter if I'm a soul?
And back in the hospital for more running.
I can still take them.
Okay, can souls put out their T-shirts?
Does Retson work on souls?
Help me.
Man, my boxers are riding up my crack.
Look, the clock doesn't figure it all.
Stop showing the clock.
You spent that nickel.
Call a call.
That's what he looks like.
Yeah.
It's 12.03.
Lunch is getting cold.
You abused your order
and violated the balance.
You know the penalty for presumption.
What the hell?
Hey, hey, hey.
Now, wait a minute.
No, no, no.
Huddle up in the middle here, movie.
Come on.
No.
You know, I don't think this movie
knows the penalty for presumption.
Let me go!
You gotta get to Summerfest, man.
Are you gonna be grieving like this
at the Grayson's dinner tomorrow?
Oh, my God, man.
That kid's from the lower class.
It's Sam.
Yeah, I'm drunk.
So what?
Hmm.
Okay, the first time the
sole must have been tilted.
It wasn't sitting in the rack just right.
Check out the headband.
He must have joined Loverboy.
Come on!
Come on, the machines!
What do I pay you people for?
You can make it.
You don't die.
Drop it.
Spit it out.
No.
Spit it.
Don't die.
Because if you die,
it'd be, like, so bogus.
I love your cloutish hair
and your pasty forehead.
You can make it.
I know you can make it.
I know you can, because, I don't know.
I can make it right.
Evan's tired of the crap, man.
There is no appeal.
If they die now, they'll be lost forever.
Lost to whom, from,
where, why, and good or bad.
Come on.
Just hop in the ring.
No, don't put me in there.
It stinks.
Oops.
There are a few medical
procedures we could try,
if you could back out of the way, please.
Remember the great
flashbacks we used to have?
The movie's story arc.
Come on.
Thank you, Natalie.
Dude's going to drive us
to Taylor Falls tomorrow.
Thank you.
Look at her go.
She's running here.
There, there, over there again.
She's like a ferret.
It's a miracle.
She's alive.
Quit pulling my hair.
Whoa, look at this.
She's darting about like mad.
So you're going to live?
Well, I'm going to need your group number.
Hey, it shrunk.
He's such a loser.
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
It's all right, Zach.
We've been waiting for you.
You're waiting for me?
We want to thank you
for saving Natalie's life.
We owe you a great deal.
Why the Katara soundtrack?
Thank you very much, sir.
We'll leave you two alone now.
All right?
Thanks, Dad.
Bye, sweetie.
Bye.
We'll see you back at the house.
All right.
Okay.
Stupid pork.
Nothing, nothing.
Surprise?
A little bit.
I have a surprise for you.
I don't have a wiener.
But that's not a de-surprise.
Oh, I broke my leg.
Can I look?
Not yet.
Almost.
The other side of the mountain of crap.
Okay, now you can look.
A plastic surgeon ready to fix your nose.
What do you think?
Oh, Zach.
Unfortunately, it's Christine.
God.
I worked overtime, so it'd
be ready before you got out.
Dude's going to come by later and roll it.
It's beautiful.
No, you're beautiful.
Yep, she did write this.
Come on.
Here's my gear head.
He's got his old soundtrack and everything.
Hey, he bought khakis.
If he could just learn to buy polo shirts and
turn the collar up, he could run in her circle.
I call it gas taker.
It's so perfect.
You know, I thought the car is Joe Estevez.
I feel like we've been
given a second chance.
What do we have?
I think.
I'm still sorting it out.
But what if he comes back?
We'll buy more hair gel.
Maybe we'll meet again in paradise.
That is none.
It's only a boiler room
at the top of a hospital.
Splash.
And what do they do
with that second chance?
Start souping up cars
and going to Summerfest.
Let's go.
I parked in the emergency zone.
Screw that stroke picker.
So, poodle hair and rubber lips drive off into the
sunset and it's sunshine and roses ever after, eh?
You seem dubious.
Yeah, Mike.
I am dubious.
I'm dubious.
My guess is that on the way home, Scrawny Boy there leans over to rub his carnauba
waxed lips on his little honey and ends up ditching that sweet ride of his.
Crow, you with me on this?
Oh, no doubt.
Things don't go near as smoothly
as Mike would like us to think.
Wait.
I didn't say things were good.
Mike's living in a fool's paradise.
Dreamer.
No happy endings for our heroes, though.
After Teen Boy puts his ride in the ditch there, he needs extra money to pay the
insurance cost and to buy a new disc sander and a couple of gallons of Bondo.
So, he takes a second job at Carl's Jr.
Yep, yep.
And about a week into his new job, he comes to pick her up in his
busted car, wearing a big orange hat and smelling a frying medium.
And she cools on the whole
relationship immediately.
Only it drags out painfully for about another month because she doesn't
have the guts to tell the second-rate Matt Latanzi to take the train.
Yep, yep, yep.
And finally, she gives him the news through the
drive-up intercom that she just wants to be friends.
And when the whole restaurant is finally done laughing at the poor Claude, he walks off the job and drives straight
to the municipal liquor store to pick up a quart of lemon-flavored gin and a six-pack of red grape malt duck.
Uh, hang on.
You know, Mike might think
that was the happy ending.
So, you guys really think I'm
a naive Pollyanna, don't you?
Um, yes, we do.
Hang on.
There's more Mr. Rose-colored glasses.
So, he drinks his way through the whole paper bag,
drives a good 75 yards, and crashes into a pole.
Well, the car hangs on to the base of the
light pole, so he can't get out of there.
He thumbs a ride back to his house, but the police arrive about
45 minutes later, wake him up, and give him the breathalyzer.
He blows a 1.3, so it's off to the
Crowbar Motel for Mike's little pal.
Well, of course, he calls his former girlfriend to come
pick him up, but Mom answers the phone and hangs up on him.
Here's one call spent.
He stays the night at the place with the
striped sunlight, courtesy of the county.
Soon, he's straining, rubbing alcohol through pieces
of burnt toast he found out behind Zelda's diner.
Oh, hang on.
Wait a minute.
I think that's a touch bleak.
Well, you know, maybe you're right, Mike.
Maybe they have a wondrous, frilly
wedding in the frou-frou land of bunnies,
where magical fairies
blow kisses to the stars,
and polka-dotted toadstools sing good ship lollipop
to the tiny mice in their little feety pajamas.
Okay, and there's nothing in between.
It's either grain alcohol in back alleys, or
a happy world of rodents in feety pajamas.
Yes!
I mean, why is that so hard to accept?
You know, you guys need help.
You really do.
Jeez.
What's with Mike?
Grain alcohol through toast.
So, uh, how'd it go, Joel?
Uh, it went pretty good.
I did have some trouble, though,
with the digital switching module.
It was all greasy.
Yeah, Mike here tried to
patch it with strips of bacon.
Oh, well, uh, I've updated
all the necessary systems.
You shouldn't have any problems for the next 10
years or 20 million miles, whichever comes first.
Uh, you know what?
I did want to show you
this fuel filter, though.
You see all that gunk
that is building up in there?
Ew, yuck.
That's got to affect performance.
Yeah, it sure does.
It's a good thing I happen along here.
Now, if you'll just sign
this, uh, I'll be on my way.
Okay, well, thanks a lot.
Sorry about that.
I don't think about my fuel filter.
No, that's the thing.
People don't think about it.
Oh, you know what?
Pearl's calling.
Hang on.
Yeah, you can pay me now.
Pay me later.
Yeah, no, I hear you.
Joel?
Is that Joel Robinson?
Brian, look at that.
It's Frank.
Frank, how are you, Frank?
Pretty good.
Uh, been soul-stealing.
In fact, you're on my list.
I'm going to need your soul.
You know, when, when,
when you get a minute.
Uh-oh.
You better get going there, Joel.
Hey, what about us?
Can you take us with you?
Uh, no, I don't really want to.
Why?
Well, I'll tell you why.
Because the years I spent here on the Satellite
of Love were the best damn years of my life.
And I wouldn't want you
mugs to miss a minute of it.
Really?
Yeah, really.
It made a man out of me.
And maybe, just maybe, if you're
lucky, it'll make a man out of you, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
You get going and I'll stay here.
And I'll get busy being a man.
That's right.
I knew there was something
I liked about you, Mike.
And you two bots, you just keep
them flying and remember Joel, all right?
All right, Joel.
Come on, Joel.
There goes Joel Robinson.
Yeah.
Just find yourself out right out there.
All right.
Yeah.
Wow.
Wow, man.
Think about it.
A real man like that allowing
me to find my own way.
That's right.
Hey, press the button like a man, Mike.
Give it a try.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Smooth for a man.
Oh, man.
I'm going to catch hell from my boss.
I haven't brought back any souls yet.
Oh, Frank, please take my soul.
I'm not going to be using it.
Oh, no.
I couldn't, really.
Well, hang on.
Hey, brain guy.
Yo.
Oh, Frank here is going
to be stealing your soul.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're barking up the wrong albino.
I'm just a brain.
100% soul free.
Sorry.
Would someone maybe like to steal my soul?
Really?
Are you sure it's okay?
This old soul, please do
me the favor of stealing it.
Wow.
Okay.
Come on.
Please roll the old miracle.
It's slipping out now.
There.
You'll be top soul stealer in no time.
I know.
Let's play ring toss with your soul.
I knew these two would get along.
Bye.
Thank you.